## Sakti Tua Petrus Davici Banjarnahor



saktitua14@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/sakti-tua-petrus-davici-banjarnahor-8b8192186



081380223328

## Summary

Hallo.. Introduce my self. My mame is sakti tua petrus davici banjarnahor. I am work as web developer programming. And I open for new engine or new programming language. With 4 years of professional web fullstack programming. And I am a bachelor of engginering informatics.

## Experience

- Wordpress Developer (May 2018 August 2018) PT Juanto Mandiri Pratama
  - Development E-commerce view use plugin of wordpress

- Web Developer (Oct 2018 August 2020) PT Unzyp Solusi Teknologi
  - Development Client System Waskita Ready Mix online with base web
  - Development Client Microsoft Dealreg with base web.
  - Development Client Arkeolog inventory system with base web.
- Web Developer & Head Project (Sept 2020 Now) PT Teknologi Api Duasisi
  - Development Client DCG Cafee create POS System
  - Development Client Duasisi Company Profile
  - Development Payroll System with PT Duasisi Company.
  - Development Domain System Listing for save domain, username and password
  - Monitoring team in work and update progress from team.
- Web Developer Freelance Project Indonesia.tv
  - Development admin panel video streaming Indonesia.tv

## Education

- Universitas Mercu buana Yogyakarta (2013 -2017) Bachelor Engginering Informatics
- SMA NEGERI 2 Binjai (2008 -2011)
- SMP ST. Thomas 2 Binjai (2008 -2011)
- SMP ST. Thomas 2 Binjai (2005 -2008)
- SD Negeri 020268 Binjai (1999 -2005)